zevera.com 2019-11-18

# Zevera - Re-launched with a new team

## About

Zevera is an online and membership based service. Zevera combines private cloud storage with import features to access or fetch remote content. 

back to top

## Terms of Service

  1. **Definition of Service**

By accessing http://zevera.com, you are agreeing to be bound by these and all applicable laws and regulations. If you do not agree with any of this, you are not allowed from using or accessing this site. Zevera.com is a paid product. Only visiting the site or using the free trial will not incur any charges.

  2. **Membership Usage and Limitations**

With the purchase of a membership you are allowed to use the service as is for personal, non-commercial usage only. Specifically, you may not:evera.com is a paid product. Only visiting the site or using the free trial will not incur any charges.

    * share your account with multiple people;
    * abuse the service and its infrastructure for any big scale or commercial purpose;
    * use the service for harmful and illegal activity of any kind;
    * attempt to reverse engineer any service offered or manipulate the system;
  3. **Service and Membership Disclaimer**

The service on this website are provided on an 'as is' basis. The site does not make any warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, the site does not warrant any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability. 

  4. **Limitations of Damages**

In no event shall the operator or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including damages for loss of data or profit or due to business interruption) arising out of the offered services. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

  5. **Accuracy of materials**

Materials appearing on thewebsite could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Zevera may make changes to the materials contained on its website at any time without notice.

  6. **Linked Sites and Content**

The operator has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement. Use of any such linked website is at the user's own risk.

  7. **Modifications and Updates of the Agreement**

Genesis Lab may revise these terms of service for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.

  8. **Governing Law**

These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the operating company and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that location.

back to top

## Refund Policy

Payments to the site are non-refundable and final. Refunds will not be processed in any but the most exceptional cases (fraud, crucial typing error).

Individual refund requests are handled on a case-by-case basis only. The request will be reviewed within 2 business days but might take longer to fully complete.

Refunds for terminated accounts are not possible as most likely the site has already incurred significant costs in relationship with the terminated accounts.

back to top

## Privacy Policy

Zevera is committed to protecting your privacy. We want you to understand what information we collect, what we don’t collect, and how we collect, use, and store information. **We do not collect logs of your activity, no logging of browsing history or personal data content.**

Our principle is to only collect the minimal data required to operate this service. We designed our systems and servers to not have sensitive data about you. 

This privacy policy will help you understand how Zevera collects, uses, and stores information. 

* * *

### Table of contents

  * General Information
  * Personal Information
  * Aggregate Connection Summary Statistics
  * Anonymous Connection Diagnostics
  * Jurisdiction and Applicable Law
  * Storing of Information Related to Email, Live Chat, and Feedback Forms
  * Security Measures to Protect Your Information
  * Cookies
  * Third-party Websites
  * Changes to the Privacy Policy

* * *

###  General Information 

Zevera collects four types of information: 

####  (i) Information related to your account ("personal information") 

This information is collected for the purpose of administering your Zevera subscription, and includes your email and payment information, which you submit on our order page when you purchase a membership. 

####  (ii) Aggregate connection summary statistics 

Zevera collects minimal information about usage. These statistics never include anything about what the user did with the site: no data about the contents or destinations of traffic and no IP addresses are stored permanently. 

####  (iii) Anonymous connection diagnostics 

Connection diagnostics are anonymized and cannot be tied back to individual users. This is needed for billing and to check usage on our services. 

###  Personal Information 

We require you provide personal information, such as an email address and payment information, so that we can email you, process payments and respond to support queries. Important: The specific information collected varies depending on the payment method you choose. To minimize the amount of information, we encourage that you use bitcoin. 

With some forms of payment we use a third-party payment processor to complete the transaction. To understand what personal information these processors collect and store, please refer to the respective processor's terms and privacy policy. 

Zevera uses your email address for the following reasons: 

  * To send emails related to payment transactions;
  * To provide links to our Site, including password reset emails;
  * To send you updates and announcements;
  * To send marketing information, such as Zevera offers, surveys, invitations, and content about other matters in connection with Zevera (“ **Marketing emails** ”). You may choose to not receive Marketing emails by following the opt-out procedure described in these emails. 

Zevera uses your personal information only for the purposes listed in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

###  Aggregate Connection Summary Statistics 

We ensure that we never log traffic destination, data content, IP addresses. Therefore: 

  * We do not know which user ever accessed a particular website or service.
  * We do not know which user was connected at a specific time or which IP addresses they used.
  * We do not know the set of original IP addresses of a user’s computer.

We cannot supply this information because the data don’t exist. 

In order to maintain excellent customer support and quality of service, Zevera collects the following information related to your usage: 

####  Aggregate sum of data transferred 

We collect information regarding the total sum of data transfer so we know which services are popular and need more ressources. 

####  Summary 

We collect minimal usage statistics to maintain our quality of service. 

We’ve engineered our systems to categorically eliminate storage of sensitive data. **We may know THAT a customer has used Zevera, but we never know HOW they have utilized our service.**

###  Anonymous Connection Diagnostics 

We collect anonymized data used for network diagnostics. We use these data in our network tools to help optimize network speeds and to let us identify problems related servers, or ISPs. 

###  Jurisdiction and Applicable Law 

Zevera wants to keep your information private. Zevera’s registered place of business is in Malaysia, which has stricter laws concerning information disclosure than most countries. 

In Malaysia are no data retention laws, and any legal order must come from court. Information requests from foreign courts are not respected. Should we receive a valid legal order from the Malaysian Court, it is important to note that **Zevera does not keep worthy logs of any IP addresses or traffic data.**

###  Storing of Information Related to Support Tickets 

Zevera uses a helpdesk system which keeps the conversation you submit to us along with our response. The helpdesk collects your email address and any additional information you provide to us. These records are deleted manually but regularly. 

###  Security Measures to Protect Your Information 

Zevera uses best practice technical security at our servers so to prevent misuse and unauthorized access. Access to user information is restricted to only the admins on need to know basis to perform their job functions. 

We believe these systems are robust, but no data security measures in the world can offer 100% protection. 

Servers are housed in data centers with strong security practices. 

###  Cookies 

####  What is a cookie? 

A cookie is a small text file used to store information about your visit to the Site. Cookies let Zevera optimize and improve the user experience of the Site by helping us deliver certain functionalities, such as website login and language settings. The cookies we use may vary over time as we continuously update and improve our Site. 

####  Disabling cookies 

You are free to change your cookie preferences at any time. You can do this in the settings panel for your browser. Depending on which browser and device you use, you may be able to control which cookies you allow, which cookies you want to block in the future, and delete cookies. For more information about these settings, please refer to the “help” section of your browser. Note that Zevera’s Site may not work as intended if you choose to disable cookies. 

####  Zevera’s cookies 

The cookies set by Zevera enable us to securely show you information that is specific to your account. The cookies contain a user identifier, but no directly personally identifying information. 

####  Third-party cookies 

Zevera might use third-party services such as Google Analytics and Adwords. Cookies from such services are used to collect data for statistical reports and marketing. 

Zevera uses Google AdWords remarketing to show advertisements on third-party websites (including Google) to users who have visited our Site. We may show such users advertisements on a Google search results page, or on a site in the Google Display Network. 

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Site. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our Privacy Policy and Google’s privacy policy. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising Opt-out Page. Users may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics Opt-out Page. 

###  Third-party Websites 

The Site may contain links to external websites that do not fall under Zevera’s domain. Zevera is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such external websites. 

###  Consent 

By using the Site, Content or Services, you agree to have your information handled as described in our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

###  Changes to the Privacy Policy 

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, without prior notice to you, consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles. Your continued use constitutes your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. 

###  How to Contact Zevera 

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy and how we handle your information, please feel free to contact us via the helpdesk. 

back to top

## Customer Service

Our customer service can be contacted here.

https://www.zevera.com/help

back to top

## Legal Information

back to top
